https://www.boordy.com/privacy-policy/

Boordy Vineyards collects personal information, including your credit card number, when you purchase products and/or memberships on our website. We do not rent, sell or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies.
We reserve the right to send you certain communications, such as announcements, administrative messages and purchase invoices, that relate to or are part of products or memberships you have purchased or agreed to obtain from Boordy Vineyards.
We are committed to protecting your privacy. Your personal information will only be used by Boordy Vineyards and will not be sold or shared with anyone. Your payment information is always safe. Our SSL software is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure commerce transactions. It encrypts all your personal information in accordance with PCI guidelines, including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannot be read over the internet.
We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products and/or services to you, or in order to do carry out their job responsibilities.
Boordy Vineyards may set and access cookies on your computer only for the purpose of improving the shopping experience when using our website, and to provide anonymous reporting for internal use only.
Boordy Vineyards may update this policy at any time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address we have on file and/or by placing a prominent notice on our site.
